thinreport.com 2010-10-28

# Privacy Policy | Thin Report

#### Introduction

 ThinReport.com respects each individual’s right to personal privacy. We will collect and use information through our Web site only in the ways disclosed in this statement. This statement applies solely to information collected at  ThinReport.com’s Web site.

#### Information Collection

 ThinReport.com collects referrer information from visitors to our website. This means we can review what search engine a user found our website from, and what ip (internet protocol) and user agent they’re using. We also collect demographic data in order to better understand our clients’ needs.

We verify the accuracy of this information using complex proprietary tracking software.

We may or may not employ cookies. A cookie is a small text file that our Web server places on a user’s computer hard drive to be a unique identifier. Cookies enable  ThinReport.com to track usage patterns and deliver customized content to users. Our cookies may or may not have an expiration date. Our cookies may or may not collect personally identifiable information.

#### Information Usage

The information collected by Thinreport.com will be used for marketing purposes. Users who provide information may receive email announcements or advertisements.

Registered users may or may not receive additional announcements from us about products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications.

The information we collect may or may not be used to create customer profiles based on browsing or purchasing history. We will not supplement information collected at our Web site with data from other sources (such as credit history to authorize purchases).

We will not share data with any third parties.

We offer links to other Web sites. Please note: When you click on links to other Web sites, we encourage you to read their privacy policies. Their standards may differ from ours.

If our policy on information collection or uses changes, we will advise you by updating this page.

#### Access to Information

 ThinReport.com maintains the accuracy of our information through ongoing content refreshing Users may access their own personal information and [contact us](http://www.thinreport.com/contact-us.html "contact us") about inaccuracies they may find.

#### Data Storage and Security

 ThinReport.com protects user information with the following security measures: secure servers, firewalls, SSL encryption and other technologies.

#### Personal & Confidential Information Usage Policy?

Any personal information (E-mail address, Phone numbers, fax numbers, physical address) and medical information is only used for correspondence with the viewers and is never used for marketing purpose. This information is also not shared with any third party.

#### Advertising Policy & Site Funding

“All the advertisements on the site are contextual to the topic and dynamically placed by Google. These advertisements can be utilized by the viewers… This is the only source of funding for maintaining the site.”

#### Editorial Content & Advertisements

“For the benefit of the viewers, ThinReport clearly mentions ‘Advertisement’ on its website in order to distinguish the editorial content from the commercial content (advertisement).”

#### Product Endorsements Policy

“We do not endorse any healthcare product and any links to a recommended product is solely for the purpose of viewer information. Our intention is to direct the customer to the sites which we have referenced for our research. We do not recommend any product purchase from any particular manufacturer. Also, ThinReport does not have a funding mechanism by way of Clicks made on a particular link.”

#### Google Adsense and Third Party Advertising

We use [Google AdSense](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/AdSense) and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads  
when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used, please click here:  
<http://www.google.com/privacy.html>

#### DoubleClick Dart Cookies

Google AdSense uses the DoubleClick DART cookie to gather the information specified above. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize cookies on your browser. You may decline to provide personal information to them and/or refuse cookies in your browser, although some of features may not function properly as a result. For more information on the DoubleClick DART cookie and privacy:  
<http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx>

**This[Privacy Policy](http://www.thinreport.com/privacy-policy.html "Privacy Policy") was last updated on 03-21-2009**
